[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Major League Baseball"]}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Why is A-Rod being singled out for what seems to be special punishment?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "A-Rod", "being", "singled", "out", "for", "what", "seems", "to", "be", "special", "punishment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Well, I think it's the nature of what Major League Baseball is alleging here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "the", "nature", "of", "what", "Major", "League", "Baseball", "is", "alleging", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Yankees"]}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Where is their integrity in all of this?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "their", "integrity", "in", "all", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Well, the Yankees really didn't want him around as we know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "Yankees", "really", "did", "n't", "want", "him", "around", "as", "we", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "But why you can't the other sports and the authorities that run them do what is happening in tennis and golf?", "question_tokens": ["But", "why", "you", "ca", "n't", "the", "other", "sports", "and", "the", "authorities", "that", "run", "them", "do", "what", "is", "happening", "in", "tennis", "and", "golf", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Actually, today, Piers, this is a great day for baseball.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "today", ",", "Piers", ",", "this", "is", "a", "great", "day", "for", "baseball", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "What's your take on it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "take", "on", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "All the above.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "the", "above", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "And has not been playing that well.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "has", "not", "been", "playing", "that", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "We have to trust again that the next wonder kid is going to be clean?", "question_tokens": ["We", "have", "to", "trust", "again", "that", "the", "next", "wonder", "kid", "is", "going", "to", "be", "clean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "I don't know that we can ever trust again.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "that", "we", "can", "ever", "trust", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNS", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Well, you know, once you're into that mindset, anything goes, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "once", "you", "'re", "into", "that", "mindset", ",", "anything", "goes", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "And yes, that is true.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "yes", ",", "that", "is", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "For those of you who think you should have intervened and done something to help the boy physically, what is your response?", "question_tokens": ["For", "those", "of", "you", "who", "think", "you", "should", "have", "intervened", "and", "done", "something", "to", "help", "the", "boy", "physically", ",", "what", "is", "your", "response", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Well, my response to that is, it's been policy that bus drivers do not jump in the middle of a fight.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "response", "to", "that", "is", ",", "it", "'s", "been", "policy", "that", "bus", "drivers", "do", "not", "jump", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "a", "fight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Do you believe with hindsight you could have done anything else than what you did?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "with", "hindsight", "you", "could", "have", "done", "anything", "else", "than", "what", "you", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "OODY: In hindsight, I followed policy.", "answer_tokens": ["OODY", ":", "In", "hindsight", ",", "I", "followed", "policy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "But how do you feel personally about what happened?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "personally", "about", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "I took it really personal.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "took", "it", "really", "personal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "What is your reaction to what the police chief said there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "what", "the", "police", "chief", "said", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Well, I - I didn't want to move the kid.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "-", "I", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "move", "the", "kid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Should we be focusing on what these three little barbarians did?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "we", "be", "focusing", "on", "what", "these", "three", "little", "barbarians", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Well, I think it's more on me because I didn't do what people thought I should have done.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "more", "on", "me", "because", "I", "did", "n't", "do", "what", "people", "thought", "I", "should", "have", "done", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Is that fair that you're getting all the flack when these kids, these thugs, are seen on camera trying to kill this kid?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "fair", "that", "you", "'re", "getting", "all", "the", "flack", "when", "these", "kids", ",", "these", "thugs", ",", "are", "seen", "on", "camera", "trying", "to", "kill", "this", "kid", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "I don't think it's fair, no.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "fair", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Will you carry on, driving buses in light of what's happened here?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "carry", "on", ",", "driving", "buses", "in", "light", "of", "what", "'s", "happened", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "I retired, Piers, I retired.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "retired", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "retired", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "This was the final straw for you, was it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "was", "the", "final", "straw", "for", "you", ",", "was", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Yes, yes, it was a big straw too.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", ",", "it", "was", "a", "big", "straw", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "What are the key takeaways we can look forward to seeing tomorrow?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "key", "takeaways", "we", "can", "look", "forward", "to", "seeing", "tomorrow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Well, first of all, what you're seeing right now with all these embassy closures, is definitely related to what we saw and what we didn't see in terms of a reaction in Benghazi.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "what", "you", "'re", "seeing", "right", "now", "with", "all", "these", "embassy", "closures", ",", "is", "definitely", "related", "to", "what", "we", "saw", "and", "what", "we", "did", "n't", "see", "in", "terms", "of", "a", "reaction", "in", "Benghazi", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Are they basically saying, we have to look like we're doing everything we can?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "basically", "saying", ",", "we", "have", "to", "look", "like", "we", "'re", "doing", "everything", "we", "can", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "In a sense -- depends on who you ask.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "a", "sense", "--", "depends", "on", "who", "you", "ask", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"], "LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Why was manpower so lacking in Benghazi?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "was", "manpower", "so", "lacking", "in", "Benghazi", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "JJR", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "We're essentially talking about a CIA mission in Benghazi.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "essentially", "talking", "about", "a", "CIA", "mission", "in", "Benghazi", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "So, because they didn't understand, they just underestimated the threat?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "because", "they", "did", "n't", "understand", ",", "they", "just", "underestimated", "the", "threat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "And we are seeing in real time the -- the very extreme action that the American administration is now taking to try and prevent another Benghazi, aren't we?", "question_tokens": ["And", "we", "are", "seeing", "in", "real", "time", "the", "--", "the", "very", "extreme", "action", "that", "the", "American", "administration", "is", "now", "taking", "to", "try", "and", "prevent", "another", "Benghazi", ",", "are", "n't", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "URNETT: We -- we absolutely are.", "answer_tokens": ["URNETT", ":", "We", "--", "we", "absolutely", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "And -- and in the end, where do you see the culpability?", "question_tokens": ["And", "--", "and", "in", "the", "end", ",", "where", "do", "you", "see", "the", "culpability", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "You know, it goes in a few places.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "goes", "in", "a", "few", "places", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Isn't that a nice way to put it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "a", "nice", "way", "to", "put", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Very blooming.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "blooming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "How important is it, Frank Ochberg, do you think to have this house of horrors torn to pieces for -- for the victims in particular?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "is", "it", ",", "Frank", "Ochberg", ",", "do", "you", "think", "to", "have", "this", "house", "of", "horrors", "torn", "to", "pieces", "for", "--", "for", "the", "victims", "in", "particular", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Well, I think it's a good move.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "good", "move", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Frank Ochberg"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "What did you make of -- of her performance and what she said?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "--", "of", "her", "performance", "and", "what", "she", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Piers, I was right there.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "I", "was", "right", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "How realistic is it that these three young women can be liberated in the near future?", "question_tokens": ["How", "realistic", "is", "it", "that", "these", "three", "young", "women", "can", "be", "liberated", "in", "the", "near", "future", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Well -- well, I absolutely believe that they can be liberated.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--", "well", ",", "I", "absolutely", "believe", "that", "they", "can", "be", "liberated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Stockholm"]}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "What is your take on that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "take", "on", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "You know, I think the Stockholm syndrome has -- has been overplayed on some levels.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "the", "Stockholm", "syndrome", "has", "--", "has", "been", "overplayed", "on", "some", "levels", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "ORGAN: Dr. Bailey, from -- from all your work with Jaycee Dugard there and many others, what is the -- the best advice you could give these three young women from Cleveland as they try and get back to normality in their lives?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Dr.", "Bailey", ",", "from", "--", "from", "all", "your", "work", "with", "Jaycee", "Dugard", "there", "and", "many", "others", ",", "what", "is", "the", "--", "the", "best", "advice", "you", "could", "give", "these", "three", "young", "women", "from", "Cleveland", "as", "they", "try", "and", "get", "back", "to", "normality", "in", "their", "lives", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Absolutely, to not let their past define them.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "to", "not", "let", "their", "past", "define", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Bailey", "Jaycee Dugard"], "LOCATION": ["Cleveland"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "How are you, first of all?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", ",", "first", "of", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "Taking it day by day.", "answer_tokens": ["Taking", "it", "day", "by", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Do you have any idea really what may have happened?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "idea", "really", "what", "may", "have", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "No, I have no doubt that he was pursuing a hot story.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "have", "no", "doubt", "that", "he", "was", "pursuing", "a", "hot", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "He was a passionate man, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "was", "a", "passionate", "man", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Well, he loved -- you know, he loved to always challenge conventional wisdom.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "loved", "--", "you", "know", ",", "he", "loved", "to", "always", "challenge", "conventional", "wisdom", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "The NSA, Edward Snowden, and even all the chatter now, the intrusions (ph) -- this was right up his -- his wheelhouse?", "question_tokens": ["The", "NSA", ",", "Edward", "Snowden", ",", "and", "even", "all", "the", "chatter", "now", ",", "the", "intrusions", "(", "ph", ")", "--", "this", "was", "right", "up", "his", "--", "his", "wheelhouse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "DT", "NNS", ":", "NN", ":", ":", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "No, I mean, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NSA"], "PERSON": ["Edward Snowden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "I mean, it must be dramatic and occasionally pretty scary and all the other things that go with it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "must", "be", "dramatic", "and", "occasionally", "pretty", "scary", "and", "all", "the", "other", "things", "that", "go", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Well, it made life really exciting.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "made", "life", "really", "exciting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "When you look at, as I say, all the current stories and stuff, where do you think Michael would have drawn the line between what should be in the public domain and what shouldn't be, in terms of where you decide what's in the national interest to keep quiet and to publish?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "at", ",", "as", "I", "say", ",", "all", "the", "current", "stories", "and", "stuff", ",", "where", "do", "you", "think", "Michael", "would", "have", "drawn", "the", "line", "between", "what", "should", "be", "in", "the", "public", "domain", "and", "what", "should", "n't", "be", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "where", "you", "decide", "what", "'s", "in", "the", "national", "interest", "to", "keep", "quiet", "and", "to", "publish", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Well, Michael -- I mean, he was a pretty big believer in radical transparency overall.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Michael", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "he", "was", "a", "pretty", "big", "believer", "in", "radical", "transparency", "overall", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 589, "question": "You a Yankees fan?", "question_tokens": ["You", "a", "Yankees", "fan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "I'm not really but...", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "really", "but", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Yankees"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Because you're a New Yorker, right?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "'re", "a", "New", "Yorker", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Now, I live in New York.", "answer_tokens": ["Now", ",", "I", "live", "in", "New", "York", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Yorker"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", ":", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "Were you surprised by the -- the incredible outpouring of attention that Michael's death got -- the tributes and accolades that came in (ph)?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "surprised", "by", "the", "--", "the", "incredible", "outpouring", "of", "attention", "that", "Michael", "'s", "death", "got", "--", "the", "tributes", "and", "accolades", "that", "came", "in", "(", "ph", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBD", ":", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "Well, I think it's a real testament to his legacy and what he stood for, and you know, how -- what a passionate supporter he was of liberty, of human rights, of freedom, of the right to -- of the right to free speech.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "real", "testament", "to", "his", "legacy", "and", "what", "he", "stood", "for", ",", "and", "you", "know", ",", "how", "--", "what", "a", "passionate", "supporter", "he", "was", "of", "liberty", ",", "of", "human", "rights", ",", "of", "freedom", ",", "of", "the", "right", "to", "--", "of", "the", "right", "to", "free", "speech", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}]